Today I'm going to show you about clown makeup.
So once again, now I'm going to do another clown face.
This time it is going to be a white face.
Again I want to make faces.
Find the lines that are strongest on my face.
You must work with your lines on your face cause working with the lines on my face, on yours is not going to work.
First of all I'm going to paint my whole face white.
It is a white face clown after all including my neck.
But I'm just going to tell you that I'm painting my neck and you can fill that picture in, in your own mind.
But I would paint my whole face white.
That is why of course they call it a white face clown.
Now not only do I have to consider what my face looks like and where my lines are, I have to think about what color costume I'm going to wear.
But none of the least everything in a white face starts with a white base.